Megan@I think this place is too creepy.
Megan@Let's move out, all five of us.
Megan@Alex, let's go pack our things.
You@Shut up, you annoying woman.
You@You two are the most troublesome.
You@Always ruining my plans.
You@You too, take off your clothes.
Megan@Don't do this.
You@Take them off!
Victoria@What's wrong with you?
Megan@Alex, stop it!
Victoria@Are you drunk?
Emily@Alex!
Emily@Over here!
Samantha@What?
Megan@She... she's acting strange too.
Samantha@What's going on?
You@You women must all love this, right?
Megan@Stop it!
You@Look how wet you are.
Samantha@I don't care, I don't care!
Samantha@I'm leaving!
Megan@This is awful!
Megan@Alex!
You@None of you are getting away today.
Megan@Alex, you can't do this!
Megan@No!
You@That's right.
You@Why can't I have sex every day when I was alive?
Megan@Alex, stop!
You@You sluts.
You@It's such a joyful thing.
Emily@Don't come any closer!
You@Stop wearing clothes.
Emily@What are you going to do?
You@Desires are all restricted by this world.
You@As long as it doesn't harm anyone...
You@And everyone's happy...
You@There's nothing to be ashamed of.